Jhaal
Shravan Bhai and Team Your Live
Pragya-Abhiyan Thank you Hello friends
I am with you all from Profit From Pune
Welcome friends to today's presentation.
He is an ODI and
Today's presentation of T-20 is like this
It will be a great presentation
presentation will go to you and it should
Very good for multibagger stocks
If it can be proved then I request everyone
I will keep that and this is the best point
take from
We will go into this and its quality.
Very important about the company
Management should also share the participants
We will share the presentation in this video.
Om
Jhaal
loot
Hello friends, the presentation starts immediately.
If it is about to happen then you should have your pen ready on the note
keep it
Jhaal
Hello friends, I am a document way
Welcome to Profit Format.
I do it friends as this is our fourth
So for presentation quarter one results
Check out the Connect presentation we've done so far
In which Ashoka was the first to be heard
GDP shows that there is tremendous demand and
The market trend of the last two-three days
And all the fat ones are well made.
So it has already been started by our President
Ashok Sundarani had told that the talk of recession
It is ongoing but the highest demand is in India
and the number between GDP is also
If you are coming in great then this is today's cotton
Today in the series we are bringing you 6 presentations.
will present in front in which All India
Our different students at the level of
Presentations from different states will be made in this.
Mansha is from Indore, she is from HDFC Life
Friends, it's life
The life insurance sector is its lender
You can also follow SBI Life
But this will be a great presentation and you
Sales for you because it's emerging
If there is an industry then you will get very good guidance.
Our dentist Dr. friend will give
Doctor Check [ __ ] Prayagraj Spicy Salumbar
He will also talk at the tuition centre and
Our wealth is in the group of six numbers.
Can creation be made about that?
The conversation will take place today with our Anil Pal who
He is from Haridwar and is the owner of Kajaria Ceramics.
We'll talk about it above because we've all seen it.
That real estate bank is good now see the demand
has started to appear so it is because of
If the Kajaria case is good then that quarter
Free so this is in the quarter one results we
Will talk about whether to like on the level
Share and what position to take and we
Everyone's favourite Parthasarathy ji Visakhapatnam
Learn about such asset management
We will complete these guitars and civil
He is an engineer and you know Amarnath ji Thakur
Everyone must know because maximum
Presentation on YouTube and A Profit
This has been done on behalf of From, this is from Gujarat
Ahmedabad and Ahmedabad and Reliance
Will research questions on industries
Because Reliance Industries has many
If the businesses are together, then each business has a
This will help you study the bar day
Prashant Khare Sir will always remain Prashant Sir for us.
Prashant Sir will talk on the angry mobile
Indore is from Indore so friends this is good
If the presentation is ours then first of all
I am our dashing doctor, less than
Prayagraj Kumbh Prayagraj call them
I would like to vote for Multibagger which tractor and
Guidance on multi if that
Welcome Doctor, set it up
Jhaal
to maximize sound
It doesn't sound like it right now
Now!
Hello friends, I am Doctor Profit from
I welcome you all from Agra, now this
going to talk about the company
Whereas ICICI Lombard General Insurance
The company holds a multi so this is something we
I will try to go to the show
So let's find out what
Friends, one thing is for sure if
it
Keeps that tension of good company
that it puts protection first that it
If you want to know then friends about tractor
Talking about the last five years
Growth of this sector in oil
Speaking of 11.20, Vincent Kara
Friends, we expect that you will come
This sector grew by only 20% in the next decade.
Why will it be done with the piece percentage from the button?
It is also important to know this
To know the pricer insurance sector
We have two mines, first of all
What insurance penetration in stones
Penetration means friend that
GDP of any country
What percentage as insurance premium
In that country he is pure and second that
Insurance density is insurance in
What does city mean field
Intensity means that per
per capita means any person
How much insurance premium is he paying?
Play Services So if we talk about India
If we talk about India's inspection
How much earlier point is 2% while the world's
What is the average
1.00 Talking about the Sagittarius situation
If we do this then what is the intensity in inches 728
Doctors and right there about the world
If we talk about it, the world average is 809
doctors and less developed countries like this
Talking about Canada, there
is approximately
7277 dollars means one man is the strongest
He is taking insurance and ours is only 60
Another thing to note here is the paste of
The thing is that we have such low insurance.
It is because we have morning right now
No, then think about it, our copy right now
What is the per capita income but what is the per capita income?
He is Aravan 1.27 lakh per person
1.27 likes per person means how much
It happened around 16 Saurabh this news is on our site
The per capita income is 16 and it is like
The premium that the country is paying is 72
Ko means three qualities welcome and premium
But if we're doing it, we'll see it like
As our per capita income increases, we
also insuring the insurance sector
Friends, if we start then which one
Let's start pumping up Swiss industry
If we do this then our
The factors that we have in our country are
We have a good demand for plot population.
Penetration and water inside question
Meaning the density is also low, we are insurance
City is low so we will see as our income
If it increases, we will have to do it for our security.
Send us your suggestions for security.
If needed, we will look into it as well.
Light will continue to increase its investment
this and when premiums increase then this
This is another biggest protest of the industry.
Info what is the model of this
What spun to cover model before money
If a claim comes, it takes
She does it fair, otherwise her money will be
Reference: This is the model which has good
Castro gives it so it's a secret
Tractors Dress Industry Co Group
Friends, we will give insurance
Industry and Delhi Jaane Insurance
We to the industry
Quotes can see life insurance and
Non-Life Insurance Live Pimple Ace Company
There are about 20 companies in India that provide life insurance
works in the insurance sector and
There are approximately 33 companies which are non-life
We work in the insurance sector.
Non-life insurance is also further extended to 45
Can be divided into which the public sector is
Corner Private Sector Insurance
Standalone health insurance holders and
Specialization Rus Prince Our Ace of Butt
Private sector insurance comes under this
History of
If we look at India, right now in India
How are you, India's 11th
Will the problem insurance business man
What is meant by non-life insurance?
If we talk about our rank in the world
Protein if talking about 220 cricketer
If you do, total insurance in two services
Market up to and most 1.72 percent India
I will share that right now we have small pockets.
It is part of the future and we will expand it.
See Butter Beach Insurance General
Insurance companies now
Which companies are there in India that
I'm working on it so I'll look here.
that the biggest part of it goes to
Goes to New India Insurance Company
end day comes apk file number n if we
fabric that if we talk to the rest of the company
I am looking for the next private sector company.
Whose Bajaj Allianz is this sir, this and 2 minutes
Nothing that the company which is in good market
Print alarm list company keeping shares
If we talk about it, how much is the list?
The company offers only four insurance options in general insurance.
Companies are listed or ABS
What happened to the applications and what happened to Jaleshwar instead?
You can invest in what happened
We can invest in it
Like we invest in Bajaj Alliance
If I have to do it then where will I invest it or
I would rather invest in Parliament then we
Bajaj Alliance's A business
I will get a similar bank to invest in.
If you want to invest in shares business then
I will invest in this soon.
Or but for now, if we only have General
Insurance providers in listed companies
If it is poetry then I have this 41 company
gives what is available and in this the Begum
If we talk about market cap shares, then listed
Companies that have the largest market share
Whereas ICE General Insurance has
Almost 1.3 lakh in total market cap
Person IS A General Missions gets this
So if we look at the graph, the premium which
Last this cut that what size listed
Near the companies
that Banna is worth crores and its biggest
Who did you go to for general insurance?
Almost 42% and how much does the ICC have?
Almonte 10.50 crore means ICICI
This pass is as much insurance as it is costume.
Gaya has almost two and a half times more channels
What does the insurance channel mean?
Insurance in the private sector
The company is a good one and collects premiums
If we talk about pocket
So friends here we see Chief
General insurance which is approximately two and a half times
She was clicking on more premium
Almost one and a half times more profit
The ad is coming from here, why is this happening and the friend who
Comment, there is a company, we will see it.
He mostly focuses on public related matters.
Taste gives its final outcome in such a place
gives inference where the list is more
This happens if their profitability is higher than
There is not much time left on the watch which is private
Sector companies are mostly
books command a premium where their
Your chances of becoming a player are lower if
Then we look at private equity companies.
But the profitability is good there.
Friends, the village is based on this.
Talking about the margins on the back
General Inch Margin Just 4.3 Like
And IS A General's Six Point Question
What does it mean that we have good margins here?
get apk file
So if we take a look at the staff meeting of this company
Talk about what Prashant did
In the last I told that the administration
Additional Equity and Profitability
Accordingly, this dating is reported to the company
had done
For years it
What the company tries to convey is that the ICC
Chief ICICI Bank in 2001 and
Fairfax Financial Holdings Limited
It was formed and today it is the largest state of India.
Largest Private Sector General
The insurance company has been established
if you
If we talk about drinking it,
Its premium means it is called morning
Music is on downstairs, she's coming
There is motor insurance
I want to meet us in net premium
Seeing how much growth I have, I am innocent.
While the largest part of it is
That they get a lot from the motor.
Only three percent of the wives were seen.
Inches should be kept in mind and work in this manner
If we talk about its expenses, then this
Company's music poster and that of the film
Tubelight offers almost 50% off
It eliminates the cost and the group in it
He can see that cent of twenty one
Anderson
So cost sinks into growth in expenses
Get that holiday 1% got means our ES
Business had to do with it, cost from business
Even bigger, that's why we have to see
We get that our profitability is
First impacted typing so this is a little bit
So what about the mantle on this company?
If investors have confidence then this gives us Shivling
Patterns are seen that the stock
Those who invest heavily in a holding pattern
There are such as Edifice IS and Mutual Fund
etc. He has extended his stick
Therefore, from 2017 till now, the SP
I did my stick almost four times
At the same time, God also said, "Speak no sense."
If the reference is increased to 50% then this
shows that over this industry and this
Investors' eyes on the business company
So friends, let's look at its historical time.
But look what this company did, that's why
If we look at the minute premium, the last hundred
Over the years it has increased its net premium
Tax from senior to 18 times 20%
It has been done and that is where capsicum is making profits.
Talking about Friends Profit too
In the last 16 years, the state has
Friends has done 25* from 22% of things
This is a tip we'll see here in 2021 to 22
Why did he get this kind of treatment in Bigg Boss?
There was a time when there were many claims of rights.
Last year we combined it with last year
We have like time, we haven't got profit
There is research, but one thing worth noting
It is here that this company is in profit
It never locked after that.
Profit decreased two but butter is also not locked.
If it is done then where is the time to see it?
Then its effect is found in and on this
that it has established itself here in the last 16 years.
Six seven times I tightened it a little
Historical tune what happened before, now go
He must see
If we talk about
do 90
119 questions in Raw Milk of Water
If I get 20 percent growth then I
We can expect this year to end.
By the time we got thirty percent more, we got a lot
Found many terror short term equity
Expression of premium in securities
There is talk about film profit.
If you do, last year in an accident - Country
One percent growth in the ninth - 50% of this
Me - Bring the meaning of 40% here brother Prem
I did not get a lifetime and did not make any profit.
If we look at the quarters there
Quarterly profit up 98%, but friends
Should we be satisfied with 60% profit?
There should be a front for us, an expression for us
Meena's expression was that he would earn money this year.
Despite being less in number than Muslims, we are allowed here.
Good groups in the profit of Akshay Growth
We expected it to be less than our expectations.
If it comes, we can expect that the shares
By the end, this fast is for thirty percent
do
What should your expression be?
Premium Growth in Chapter 30 Percent
The growth and profit growth is also small but cent percent.
long-term we 14% Kasi mrig 14% password
expect with quote expression
and exploitation pollution view feature display
The company tweeted in 2005
We are one of the approximately fixed Rs. 13,500 crores.
We estimate that by 2030 it will be around 60-70
will collect premium of Rs. 1000 crore and
By 2035, it will be worth approximately Rs 7000 crore.
Friends must be collecting premium
Talking about benefits, in 2005
It made a profit of ₹100 crores 12:30
Valve is what we can expect
By 2030 it would be approximately 125 crore rupees.
Friends, this profit will be made.
If there is lifetime high profit then right know
There is still time to enter
Was it about profit for almost a month and a half in 2021?
14 thousand 460 14 crores right now
Expression is this 2030 in All Muskara 100
Crore Ka Karegi Means A Life Time Hai
It is going to make profits and we expect it.
We will make sure that the patties arrive in about half an hour.
Make a profit of seven thousand crores
friends
What our family should be like
Stop our family will be almost 1399 chillies
and two more
If you are expecting loot phase then this
Little
Fundamentals Value Technique of this company
Hey let's see
that this company
Right now in good because our extraction
According to this, it had to be broken and first
is quite broken so here we are
not very much
If it is seen in the middle then it
can be found in
Subscribe if
very cheap
What it means is that here the company
If the subscription is expensive then what do we have to do here?
We should do it, we should get out of here
Collect
And by 1798 there was some profit on it
If you book, is this target directly in
You will get it friends as per its results
Our profits are not in line with our expectations.
Could this company have launched another 10
Do it once
If the subscription starts then it will go to 70 80
And such a company will be given a multi-year tariff.
should be folded
And in this sector it is using its tractor
It is a master company and it is a good player in the sector.
Growth is expected from the company, we have two purses.
should be kept in
Thank you friends, this is our take on this.
This question was only for the purpose
Please
How to buy through subscription? First thanks
you thank you
Thank you, I would like to ask you one thing:
For benefits
This company of yours
It is spreading its legs like
That
For us, what we have and for Indians
So you should expect this
that this famous company
If it could not happen and it will increase then here
which is ours
For insurance
I am feeling well
And why did we change the ID to G, which is RAW
By the way, this
If we look at the listed companies, most
Best company in the list but we have more
There is no option and if we have an option
If you want to buy then like Gypsy Rod and Bajaj Bajaj
If it is of the Alliance then for that we have to
The parent company will have to pay either
Make your check in that if we just
If insurance is fruitful then I will become ICC chief but
This is where one of us should be.
Jai Hind this corrupt thank you so much excellent
Presentation Jhaal and a layer of TV came that
Why should we stay in the emerging sector?
As we saw earlier, Infosys is also a
It was near 120 in time.
was in the sector and there were a lot of base plates
If we go to Amazon like this, sir, we will never
I would like to review your presentation.
It was great that I was the ICC Chief, before that
I would like to ask about celery and other ones
How was your experience with Promise?
What's one more thing you'd like to tell me?
Because of which Bigg Boss also
Clear will be given then for my learning
The main learning that I have gained is that someone
Balance your stock investment
Where is it at, I got to know this means
This is not the reason why Bigg Boss Jodo Mein
And before joining Profit Point, my
I thought, brother, take your good dividend.
Butt mode of gangster will be found later
If the price is high then the diamond price is at the same place
I had to travel around India but could not find clear ghee.
If I was, I would know where to do it.
What to do and when to do it is most important when
College
I was lucky in shooting that I
If I find the right path soon then now
When did he get this call? I was right.
No, that's why I'm still in school
Portfolio Green Diamond But My Friend
If the job portfolio is rated, when will it be
and the second important part is
How much do I have to do, it doesn't mean I'm going high
If it is there then you take the full take and take it now
You have so much [ __ ], you don't have any, you have nothing
If the police want to make it, then they will have to make it a little bit.
Then which level do I have to come to and most of all
Important I felt that the motion control minute
Expression: Keep in mind that I am the last
If the cent is going down at thirty or 40%
If it is downloaded then my heartbeat will not increase or
Then my stop is double and so I am very
If I am not very happy then their
What should be the expectation, this is something
I got to learn something from this, what happened sir?
The best thing I liked about profit permits
I felt peace whenever
Correction is for you to take peace only then and
You will get a chance
So this is how the base price of the bank increased.
There is an expectation before the one who
learning that is very important because
When do people feel scared because they know
There is no choice as to what to take, then take it.
And how much do you want to take? You've got a good loot.
completed his education due to which he completed
In the moment you are not afraid of anything.
You need to increase your stock in the depot which
So I request this from Multibagger
I would like him to do such a wonderful presentation
It's in your comment
9th Great Feeling A Very Good
demonstration they told and mutual in this
Lagi means they will gather in line
Look at the presentation, we believe that
General Insurance is Emerging and Growing
There is going to be tremendous business on this, meaning today
Taking 10 is about to complete Avery
Thing is gold but right now the problem is it's near
You told me clearly what happens on the phone.
that June is its favorite company
I would have had good children in that only.
which again disappointed people that
He explained very well that now
Apple has not estimated its profits.
The problem is solved like that at the ATM.
It is being said that the competition will not increase profits.
You will get two or three more likes and profits.
No, we already have been testing it for 2 years.
We are sitting here, it will go from here, promise.
If he doesn't come, what will happen now because of the extreme cold?
Like short jeans pants, very well done
Clearly mentioned profit sir no
Death Stuart Broad and a short-term correction
If it stays then I will not worry but an update
And let me tell you when people here know the second
Live or General depending on the result
Insurance profits are not that good but
I will show you the bud tomorrow, that means on Friday
that SBI ran HDFC ran ICSE General
The reason behind the bomb in insurance
The reason for the result not being there is the update that was given yesterday.
Typing pack abs from Hi Dad I
Hussain has taken a very good initiative abroad.
Making direction king of products on his own
But whatever camp these people decide
that I have been given to people quite quietly and
In the future, we will be its friend.
Fanfiction profits if you look at both.
Din Aankh Maare Positive For All The Kapil
Types of Great Wonderful Presentation Dad
West of the best way Amritvarsha thank you
This is your passion for a great presentation.
Beach center is on our mobile so Prashant
Subscribe
If I do, I can make presentation on mobile.
to give because there is a mobile company and
I made a good amount of money in this, so I
Labels will also indicate
Thank you very much for the invite
So friends, now let's take another
Interesting Multibagger Well About Others
I will discuss the ones that came out recently.
The day before yesterday, the whole name of this company is
Root is the slogan of the mobile screen
Communication simplified so friends today
Now its Q1 results for 22-23 are the same.
In Simplified, we will discuss
Friends, let me start my presentation.
Before that, let me ask you a question
If someone asks you to buy a mobile phone,
If someone gives you a tip about it, will you
If you buy or what do you do then you chat box
You can write your answer in this question but
If you ask me, my answer will be
Not at all because our respected Guruji
Future and profit from soil gave us
Taught how to understand the fundamentals of stocks
Technical Edit Industry Housewives
Whether the talk has quality or not, then on that basis
But we address the top through
Friends, let us start our Give Wealth
Stage whose results came just the day before yesterday
So friends, first of all our basic work
If you want to edit the tractor then friends
Root Mobile which is owned by Yadav Telecom Service
If BJP has kept it in the sector then
Friends, factor analysis is inside this
The most important thing is industry growth.
Friends
As soon as we see the interesting form of the slide
Inside, in the last 14 years, about 5
Industry growth at a CAGR of 20 per cent
Brightness is increased and short term
See, within 50, 60% of them are from this friend.
Friends, another crop has started again.
I ask you if this growth is good.
Or it is bad, you can write it in the fire stomach box
And that's pretty good if you ask me.
Growth as it gives the GT more performance
If she is doing this then definitely we are growing so much
The focus should be on the industry itself
So friends, now we are in the senior group.
If you do the fundamental values ​​of then you can bar
Total Art is a company in the telecom sector and
First of all, if you look at the market cap, then
The total of factors that determine the market performance of 18 companies
The cap is now coming to around Rs 190.28 crore.
Friends, what is market cap, it is
It's so simple that you can calculate it yourself.
Current market price multiplied by
The number of total shares you get from the market
If we get it, then inside it we see that
Route Mobile is the most popular mobile phone in Western Europe.
are giving importance or they feel that
Definitely if he invests in this company
If he does something, he will come back and get angry here.
What 40% market share of mobile gives it
Cut number which is of Sterlite Technology
Is
Their market share and market cap are around 40%.
and about 50% of the retail is of Aeron Mobile
seven point one percent that now friends we
We will talk about it later, so here it is four
You can see the face of the companies because
Friends, once we discussed profit from pet.
I learned that companies that specialize in this are not
If she did, why did you waste time on it?
Do it because if you cannot pay the salary
Where will the profit come from if it is less then definitely
Here we look at kissing technology.
Paris holds approximately 59% of its shares.
And the same trend is 20% for mobile and 60% for retail.
Now friends, one thing you did in your previous job
I am from the market, the slide that was there
Inside we saw that the angry mobile
Investors are giving the most importance
for investment and this Sterlite
Even though technology has more oil
If you are not giving importance to it then it
Why, we will answer this in the coming section.
If you are looking for it, friends, here you will find it.
You will get the answer because total companies which
This profit tax is approximately Rs 451 crore.
is making a profit of more than
Its profit is talc, which is frustrated
But friend, here comes Root Mobile Thirty again.
Give close to nine percent and light on
Technology is close to 11:00 percent, so
Friends, here in the activity we have some
I am looking messed up now, so much tanning and we
We will know when we add quality.
Which company is of quality and here
But if we can focus, we grow.
On to the next flight, friends, let's go.
Quality edits take into account this factor.
Friends, you are the best male indicator.
You can find out on the melt side which one
The management of the company is smart and good.
He takes the money he earns home and
Can also make investors earn money
So here you will see that Root Mobile
This net profit is around 8%.
margin because the average tractor's net
Set the profit margin to judge and this
We see a dot in cross technology
One percent of retail net in 14th
Take the profit margin and start a company called Mobile
I have a net profit market of 3%
Now friends, let us look at liquidity
From the reversed Yagnik current pressure we get this
It appears that in the short term the company
has no financial problems and this
The current track of the company is 1.19
So here we see that the Rooth mobile which
that and is performing sometimes in a group
The company has to track its current status there.
It reached 185, then on mobile came at third place.
1.72 and then retail 1.30
Technology is 1.02 now we see
Friends, solvent, then one thing is here
How much debt is there in relation to equity?
So here we see that about three
The companies are on debt: Root Mobile Retail and
Top of the flight technology on wholesale mobiles
So we see the Hide AB Enhancement button.
So this depression is due to excessive buying, so we
Investing in other companies
We should be careful, let's talk now.
Depression, friends, here I have
The liability of SMS is taken
If it is placed in front of you then the average
Which is the depression of the industry in the sixties.
Root Mobile is approaching five percent
59% add of then 727 of Sterlite Technology
President RailTel's Forty Seven Percent
Aeron Mobile has 20% now friends talk
What is the interest coverage ratio or
Paying capacity is what we look at here.
That Ruth Mobile's F-35 is Tubelight
Technology has two retail photos and
If you don't have any fat on your mobile then friends
Here the higher the number the higher the ICR number
That company will have that much to invest
The paper remains now friends, return on
Talking about equity, Root Mobile
Sterlite's return on equity is ten percent.
2% of Technology is 40% of Airtel and on
Mobile has 2%, now we will talk about written
On the topic tweeted by Initial Joe
Compared to the money invested
How much profit does he earn every year?
Root Mobile's inverters stop working almost every year
Which is three times more than its price.
Sterlite is making profits
Nearly 1x that of technology and retail
One more fold and mobile
Phone now friends talk returns and
If you want acid then friends, root your mobile.
Invest what is ten percent greater
Noida is getting this kind of technology
This one percent and per center belongs to Airtel.
And we are 2% of mobile and total this sector
If we look at the average, it is close to three percent
Return form acid clean so friends you
Whatever you present on the side, it is something or the other.
There must be confusion because many
Railtel which is there and was performing somewhere
Angry mobile somewhere else on mobile friends who
We look at other companies because our
People are wealth, group plus quality is difficult.
to wealth so in other companies we get that
According to him, Tej Group is not a profit group.
Found what we see in Root Mobile
So that's why I took us to a senior group
Which is the best company in Roop Mobile
If you see it, then now think about it from this side
Let us first discuss
Bay Clear Time's company called Root Mobile
How have you behaved near me?
Slice profit boil in the coming days
How can she behave, so let's see friends
We start with the science route
Friends, first of all I will tell you about mobile
Let me tell you that this route is mobile business.
If it has been done then 90% of their revenue
Digital Native He knows clear lineage
60% of the time the partner does not come
Warts cut off thirty percent of the profits
Telecom and Allied accounts for approximately ten percent.
Eight percent of retail travel comes from services
And hospitality is three percent.
Friends, let me tell you the simple side, fruit
Mobile particular communication and messaging
Leo is in business like you are now
You see, Congress has launched its online
Chanakya Phatka, you get a message
Some banks receive delivery messages.
You made a transaction or made a deposit
Did his messages come from you then?
You booked a plane ticket for travel.
Gave me a train ticket and a bus ticket
If you book, you will get all these immediately.
If the message comes, it will be strong.
There is a tractor industry here.
Definitely we should cut it guys
We see that the IPO of Route Mobile is
It came in 2008, so I have it since 2016.
Do this till the company's cycle sells for Rs 4 crore.
It used to generate revenue of Rs. 10000 which has now increased to Rs.
In 2022, it has now become Rs 2002 crore.
If you look at this oil, it is about 42%
that their compound group by cells have some
If the tilak of Time SIM is increased then it is very
GDP is performing very well
Apart from this, let us talk about profit growth.
If that person has ₹10000000 in 2016
Their profit has now increased
170 crore care has been almost done in these three
times the profit in previous years
Increased and profit is hair growth
If we look at the printed percentage, this is their
The group has grown now friends on this side
How much profit is there in just one time?
which had reduced within 2018
Hello friends, let's talk about heavy pain.
Its sales in 2016 were only Rs 121 crore.
The result has now increased to Rs 210 crore.
60% off on MS Word in your recharge
The rise and record of the Tango Line
To further his acting career, he had to
The thing is that they get funding from outside as well.
If it is there then definitely when I know it then
Returning is increasing and so is increasing
and this is not the company's retainer but its
determines book value
Now friends, let's talk about net profit.
Historically, we will see that the margin
Last ad which has increased by 6% in six years
to a net profit of seventeen percent
Business has been done above margin, now let's talk
Let's do it, let's see the history five
It gives you oil profit and but what now
This is its condition, know why the day route was closed
How is the performance of the mobile?
So friends, let's talk about it next time.
If you look at the slide, friends, here
I have profit after tax GPS
Last 4 of setting Net Profit Margin
Quarterly data given and percentage
Wise I explained growth
So here in one we see that oil
Which is 2030 percent, their ninth was bigger
I grew up faster than one percent of the family, then
Residents saw a rapid growth of 44% and
Why do something amazing while you are in pain now?
Gave us 95% of Facebook to see
Friends, we are getting it inside Tej.
Straight is visible from last 4 quarters
Now those who talk about profit, then one
We made a profit of 11:00 percent in the bar.
Ninth saw a profit growth of 12%
This was in our eleventh annual result.
Which is why we saw a profit growth of eight percent.
was and
This time in life it has done wonders
Outperformed by SEND at 109
Profit growth given this source so far
Don't rape friends, this is the last time.
Which is GPS growth, once it is told
I am 11:00 percent, nothing in my opinion.
Cent and Environment Will on the Trail
Present A and St on et inside life
And last year, the history group is their less.
That's why it's growing compared to profit
Because last year these people did only a few
The equity was created through Vapi.
So he directly becomes a shareholder and then a partner.
If they have gone, then that is why its arrow is on history
The effect has arrived
Now let's talk about the fruits of last year, last one forest
I had a margin of nine percent in one
The ninth had an annual margin of nine percent.
I saw a one percent margin, God.
Kumar Jain has also increased to ten percent.
Now friends, let's talk about the major of
After doing the main business of the company
We will see where the cost is incurred.
Their main business is Message Bank Center.
If it runs from then almost all the ads inside it
Percentage cost has increased Employee Stock
The option is that the cost increased by 95%, this again
Actually, uncle needs a finance course because
Last year jkt48 lax that time
Finance for which has increased to about four
crores, then we see that others
Here the expenses have also increased by about 75%.
Now friends let's talk
Ko pregnant delivery so friends
Statement is their revenue in India
If you do it on the previous wife [ __ ] then Chiffon India's
Inside their segment revenue business lay
And he talks about the rest of the world
So their payment release increased by almost 99%.
If this has happened then friends we should understand one thing from this
Root Mobile's main business comes in
The songs are coming from outside India.
Now let's talk about current trends in stomach.
Here I have written the history of four quarters.
If it is taken then the way in which trail EPS
It seems that the trail is before history.
Now let's see any positive that which is 2820
It was this and this is the only trail
From the quarters we see that almost torn
It is around ₹3, friend, this is his annual quit
is performing
Now let's talk about future expectations
I have seen the current train but brother, I have not yet seen this
In the year 2030, in 2030, in 2035, their speed
Quilling for profit, what is sand
First of all, if we had talked about 2023 then this
In the year, I hope that 50% of the groups that
that I took quite reasonable and inside they
Watching TV, this Tata is a life
Looking at the results, it is worth Rs 3000 crore.
The nearest hill to them may be in 2030
I expect that whatever their face is
approximately
could be around Rs 240 to Rs 10 crore and
A tractor in 1235 is equivalent to about 135 cars.
Their victim lives closer to the hilt now
As far as profit is concerned, this year
I hope they get 255 products.
It expects to be profitable in 2030
I am that the closure of Zulfiqar fuel
There will be profit and in 2015 it will be Rs 300 crore.
Their profit is almost as far as the stomach is concerned.
As far as the thing is, we have now installed Trail GPS.
I saw about 130 fruit cars, I hope
I promise that this year their
IPS may come close to Rs.32
It may remain close to 178 in 2030 and 1235
I live around 150 now, friends.
What about investing in the stock market
The advantage you have over fixed
If you see, then fixed rate in this your army
For the fifth year you had the jeans pant rate
You get it in the morning where you have deposited it.
It doesn't last, but you can see it on this side.
We have to see that his IPS continues to increase.
and this will be our income and this will be our loss
If I try to create our belt, this year
Check out its fundamental bike value
So it is coming around ₹90 by 2030
Inside we see the value is around 1800.
back scrunch method or and in 1235 we see
that the poor
His affair around Twenty20 is busy
Now friends share holding remains
If you had a look at the pattern,
In comparison to 2020, this is what the promoter
year which is about one percent of your tax
Mutual funds have also reduced Sid's interest on Kotak Mahindra Bank.
Which was his in 2019 right now at six per cent
The stake has dropped by around 1570 percent.
The tag has been removed but the points will remain.
Those who have inverters are the first ones to say
has read its statement at 6% and retail
Investors have to be commended for their
People have a bigger one than one percent
12% tax has been paid or approximately
15 cents in these have increased
That now friends, these are some investors
The presentation impressed me with Fruit Mobile's roadmap.
How to group the map found by the company
So this company started in 2004 and
You can see the graph of the company directly today.
Is rising high in terms of performance
Now let's talk about their global
In business, we have seen that
IPL Team India in Africa Middle East
This is the only place where no role can be played while operating.
From deployment to a universal flour center
1000 employees' bags were broken in a week
Plus the above network is theirs
That now friends, in this side I am the main
I will talk about it in detail that I had five
from leaders within the business and that
It is estimated that it is around 9 million now.
Vista Business
Head which increased to around 3511 in 2012
If it is going to happen within 2036 then Root Mobile
This is the view that is on this and inside it
If the companies win the week,
Definitely have to do maximum share game
Now friends, I would like another company
So here
These people opened it inside and gave it to the customers.
Joe was called near and served to him that
As long as their payment is also made on top of the communication
Delivery will also be good
And friends, there is one more thing worth noting.
that the Government of Assam delivers critical
communications2 One million plus cities with
Help of root mobile communication body and
This service is reversed in the relief camp in Assam
Government
Help me a lot and also help the citizens a lot
Please help me
Sorry now friends any
Review of new products for that company
Momentum is very important and it is emerging
It is a company in the industry because other
Companies now we have in the form of spear
We will see the relative business in small steps.
is different and communication so we know that
How much technology has affected us today?
Becoming a partner in day-to-day life
The PM Maximum game is his and
Definitely the company is cutting it down.
Now friends, technically Vijay is fundamentally
We have seen that approximately
Whose foot behavior is around 80 on
Technically, where should we buy it?
Friends in Profit From Midnight
Which I will repeat to you again.
Hoon Pro Plus Quality Plug Delhi
Investing in good stocks at least gives us
If you should buy it at a price then technically it
If we look at it, you can see it around 1275
can be activated and its short term
The target which is coming is around 2323.
It is coming and I have a long term target.
You have talked about a fundamental right.
So friends, my confusion is that we
In this, give 2% in location portfolio
If possible, then we can put ₹2 in it.
Now you will ask that we
Friends, the simple answer is that a small company
This and his main business is arrest.
You come from all over the world and also from India.
But what is their main expense?
Message bike center inside it if the fluctuations
If it happens then definitely it is ours
It can affect the investment
So we should give it two percent of our
Application to Ruth Mobile in portfolio
There is no doubt that teacher wealth should be given
Creators talk about emerging industries in
Two
If yes, then friends, give this in the disclosure.
I want this presentation back to school
Education Per Breast-Fruit Deliver Financial
Advisor for Buying and Selling and I
I want to thank you very much for our
Momentum Doctor Million Sir and our respected
Guruji is the one who gave me this platform.
I gave my all like this
123 Local Route Mobile Result Family Pick
Thank you very much for doing
Ya thank you Prashant Sir Emerging Industry
and discussed a multibagger from
Gave a great presentation because your
He gave a presentation and I was very
It moves
If you are crazy about subscription then you people
and not to take into account
If you tell me a good one, I would like to know
I want that from my side only, whose
choose well because they are friends
Is his vision also of 10 years or are you telling me that
what will happen after 10 years in 2022 then I
I would like to know this from you Lights Arvind Sir
Actually I am March 2017 which is online
I was a student at that time and my
Someone with a financial background and maths
And this is what you can do with slide presentations in Google Sheets.
I had nothing to do with the flight, but
I want to thank Future
He did all this with the profits from
I did a course from him and I learned everything.
I have got it and if not the best love then I have got this
that is
If there is a fall, I am more happy that when
I should add more and make a big profit from it.
Midnight login remember that by doing
Form and weather rally so definitely us main
We wait for the fruits inside any file
While doing the rally one goes but one
I feel like all this is coming to me quite late.
Taking me in which this is now my retirement
The time is coming but I think it is better
I tell the young generation that it is better late than never.
I want to give the message that he is as right as
Quickly your investment process and respect
grind it properly and teach us if he
According to the stock, Mellitus will make profit
If we combine this then it will definitely be one
He has achieved tremendous wealth creation in his life.
If you can see then thank you friendly use sir
For the guidance you have given
used answer but along with that this also
I would like to say that the students also put in a lot of hard work.
It's been important since I saw you
If you have homework then do the most in your match also.
Did a lot of good work and every presentation
I don't think you have any yet
If the presentation is done properly then it is your
It is also the result of hard work and dedication due to which today
We're watching this great presentation.
What I want to know about Root Mobile from Future
Also, the presentation person is to live his
I would like to take a drink about the government
Mean by root so how long have we been
Track SIM type or suicide
Why I had companies that had many attendees and people
has interest in many companies
I think I lost because I was in the company
People have to deposit money and they have to
I should remain active in this way.
My mind is like ginger fields
I think you guys have been following my IPO ever since it came out.
Who thinks you are giving me a package advance?
Tight Trussack promoters say we
If you do a major search, your
Trust falls, you will notice the beginning
But we used to call it one percent powder.
I don't know what the promoter will say in a week.
How will we do it next, but as
Trust keeps growing that people are very good
Come and see, I think I don't recognize the cover.
I've done it and I'll call you back on it.
I would like to say that we all thought that we would fail this time.
The children did not come
Some will break in the 9th, their growth oil is ready
These people developed because of being good students and
Doing good business in the country
So look at these on the back side of your companies
It is necessary that he also knows that it is bad.
There is still time, but let's see how we start our business.
Both organically and inorganically
These people grow and see, they experiment.
In such a company, there is a way to move forward in bad times.
If we can sit for a long term then today's
Prashant ji's presentation seems to be
Then it will not work because that city
I have broken hope but I did not enjoy it.
But suddenly the most explosive result of good results
If you stay then it will depend on others.
Opportunity and Best Time to Learn About
Note: I think Prashant ji actually
Life was supposed to perform next week.
It means a completion due to some sudden
So what is some general that could happen
Yes Prashant ji could have said tide to MT
I will not be able to do it but I will promote it.
commitment we have already seen that only then
They will fry till their time comes, they think tomorrow
The results are out and you have everything ready today.
If you don't like it that much then Feet Patna
Patna Result Updating Tagged
Is it true that all the barrels should be activated, so this
Prashant ji, I am very high budget young
Working to motivate people
Thank you very much and best of luck
Happy Yaduvanshi very much for yours
Thank you, thank you, when so friends, next jo
The presentation is always from Indore, so I
Shanti will tell us about life.
I
IT Professionals and our best
If you are a presentation presenter, then tell me.
I would like to today
We are a discussion industry, so about one
There is also a lot of discussion and many people
hope in their lives
by making money
He will find out and everyone will know about it.
will add and
Product Best Student
Friends, today I am in front of you all.
Quarters
[music]
to
I've already taken a watch
Friends, I have brought the other aspect before you.
I am the brother campus, what kind of tractors are these
On that because you send this message to everyone
has tweeted, my affairs also did
and we should also select here
If we look at this, we have pension plan which
Let's take it, that too comes from the tractor side
We have a retirement plan and protection.
Like it protection also those who do the challenge
All the details of the child's action plan will remain in the middle.
Whatever comes is from that tractor.
Come on friends, now I am your
Without taking much time, let me start with
Presentation Talk Tractors Him
Tractor is a very important thing which
We all have seen it because when we go to any page
If we are investing in Gujjars
If we don't have an idea in the sector, we will be cheated.
can
Friends, first of all tractor channel white
The most important point is that this group
This is a group, without him, without the village.
Any investment, try us and test the vapor
If you can't then first of all we saw the point today
The life insurance sector, which is
If there is a part here then if I we
If you see, so much penetration means India.
How many people live in
Gujjars have insurance
Patience can buy them at 20% off
fixed at around nine percent of
Can there be three points in India
2% penetration is used a lot but still more
India still has a very long journey to go.
If seen on density white
3900 and here if we look, there is a
No word no, now that density of dollars here
Friends, as I told you, here
But we have got life protection at least.
Pension plans and as seen in 2019
Today we keep Life Explained as normal
We have to keep the 78th anniversary of the person's arrival.
in the next few years, even after two years, this year
next week okay okay and this thing is our
Retirement age will be dealt with by the eyes
There will be security for the people there that this
Also a business for the human sector
Growth of population is what we see.
Look at the competition we still have today.
Sixty-five Years - Coming Soon
In the future also we are looking at 20%
Most of our population will remain young.
There will be a population that will take insurance
will like and remain in insurance
We expect a population of one billion.
Bikes that will be insurable by 2030 5
Hello friends, let's discuss our today's date.
Look at what has happened and look at the population, it is so
Picture Saver Mode on Thousand Words Watch
Army population, today we are feeling so special
This address is for market people who have patience to purchase
You can do it in the additional market from tomorrow
It is available but how much can we uninstall now?
This is all that is left now, so usage growth and
Who is worried about protection baby?
Look, if we look at the protection gap,
Liability protection from Amazon
Here you will find a protection gift
Pimples Mantra for Protection of Our
Vivek, we will be worried about you.
Let it nourish us well
Isn't this the best trend of divisional?
right if we look at 2010 here
Click
So if you
Our
Now the company to be owned by the government
So in comparison to that
Continuous job in private sector since 2016
doing
to the interested
doing the above
If you go into some industry
We have this
know that
Our
For
Subscribe to
Which is the confusion regarding long term defects?
This will help customers to participate in the company.
We will be old public sector companies
Like LIC, we invest seven percent there.
Expect growth and fall to earth
Talking about the private sector long term
There was a growth of just 100 percent.
Expect it, but we still like it like this
Udayveer Victim Percent Key Group Expectation
One can talk long-term
So this is me short term 500 long-term 2006
that we are talking about
Aditya, let's talk about market capital.
If we look at where the money is in the market
Total if we look at the tractor and retail
Companies Group Office Tree Listed Companies
There is life insurance in this sector
If you look at it there, today it is with LIC.
Then Sanskar's market share is on T3.
We have taken it into trend and we are going private.
The sector is dominating and we are private
Set the bramble of the sector on the table
Click By removing doubt, we can help the private sector
Just try glycemic SBI
Lead
34.33 market share seems to be there
HDFC Life Thirty One Percent
Find the cross area near and ICICI
There is also Prudential Life Insurance
If you like Twenty One, here we are.
Look, this visit, this part is 60% private.
If these two companies are doing it in the sector
If you see the topless program then LIC, SBI and
HDFC Life is coming to us now
Where is this Churma cricket market money?
It's going too far, let's talk now please
If Jhaal Pooch Dua says so then if the thing
If we look at it from the top line, right now we
Talk here Dil To Brilliant Club
75% Peer Chief LIC is the red button friends
We should keep this in mind LIC
Life is India's oldest company.
Insurance that when I used to have Ray
Then LIC Presents Edison
More on SBI Life Insurance
so
Subscribed and in which companies too
If we
Click Company in Private Sector
Subscribe and we'll provide proper and
Where is it now, we will campaign it in Indore.
Can oil always be profitable?
I am seeing a similar picture as in digestion.
LIC is giving 50% profitability in front.
Is
If we remove this paste
We are recognized as the Most Talented in Profitability.
Person
More
This is also in top player properties.
We are into quality checkup
Subscribe because
Sure
Subscribe and
We have
Friends at SBI Life
The first thing you should look at is the profit margin.
Who is taking away how much profit?
Let us look at LIC which is our oldest and
Plug is a public player, that is also possible.
Traders stop this without taking profits
In person if we look at SBI Life
with 6 more
can like what was last year
There was a video there, click on it and
And there the profit margin of the company
were falling
it
company's
tell and do the whole story
So important for today
I want to invest and I will get returns.
Money flowed into the company
Yes, but if such an investor gives me money today
If I invest, how much return will I get?
At the end of the year, friends, many times
The accused can also give you this lead, so
If I take this teacher in this manner, then first
LIC is accused of torn while discussing the army.
SBI Life does not have 30%
SBI Life's
So friends, here you will get profit divide.
do it
in which our equity means this chapter
The Protein Upanishad from Didi Investors
Capital had blasted in all these years
Those who can say this by doing business, who reserve
They have created quality in the company.
That bridge is to improve you and we are going to create a portal.
If we look at equity, friends, look at LIC.
which is equity total
The lowest profit
He has been with such an old company for a long time.
4000 only, 4000 crores only, approximately
So
If you haven't subscribed to this
Taking thousand crores from there and here
means school
Subscribe, this is important
Quality 9 percent Hota Eid
Responsible This is our thing understanding map
That now let's move forward and stop the persistence pressure
Understand this as if you have purchased insurance today.
Policy taken for next year's insurance
premium refunders because we take
If so, then its shift is minimum
And we're going to pay next year's premium.
near her husband
Coming back
So
Subscribe to
Butter is being seen after five years
subscribed
subscribe to yes here we are
How much is this business in persistence regions?
The dress is being made, now let's talk friends
Hmm, I don't like this quality LIC.
Used to be
because it is public and
Now SBI and HDFC
Now that I like you
To avoid being deceived, we will fulfill that
Like
Subscribe
[music]
Tax
has been taken
5000 in 2009
[music]
crores were made
It has happened in 13 years and is famous for looting
If we are getting cent CAGR then this
Nothing good can happen and here
But if you look at what we've seen this year
Expectation Refill
Friends, if I look here, how many
I felt like I was immersed in the year
has been continuously increasing
And I mean no less than any company
Know how to do it
Now let's talk about profitability.
If the company noesis is turned on last then there
But there is a little bit left, see the company has a
Bar Company as Profitable as in 2012
From there to last year, Djokovic had this
Friends, where do you clean the most?
We were there, we took a look at the company.
Continues positive, never forget
Profit should be in the last ten years
What a great thing and look at them here
Recovery Slow We must remember that
Profitability down 2% last year
Now let's talk about some prices.
Life's IPO has come, if we look at it, arrange it.
And if you look at every range, this is not happening.
Is
Our expectations for this year
We are seeing that between the years
share in
should do
Now let's talk
So that
Me
My property
[music]
Would
many times even
He did it here like this
From there we come to our place on Idli
The distance factor, as we saw
Behind the profit less last year
Major reason is because of the right reasons that our
pass which
Today on the claim side of the movie he is a criminal
petrol
take the loot
While taking here we are talking about this company
and second
Subscribe also
This company has
Subscribe now here we are
And
Are you subscribing?
How much trouble they are causing this company
He is shopping for it
So friends, now let's talk about term results
Update
Please gift it to our next
This becomes our baseline for the destination.
In the quarter this year friends we saw
That our love for group 3118 is very
Fabulous
Very friends here is one more thing
that whatever premium we pay friends, it
The company invests it and you invest 70%
Later some gas is also available in the market.
It seems like Hi Dad likes to stay in the middle.
And also invest in the stock market
So here we look at these things.
Investment in these is low and there is no editing.
Come
Friends, this year is ours, whatever it is
If there is profitably impact of then here
The reason is that there is vibration interest on it.
The rate hike here has an impact on the debt market.
This is our pizza that we were having
The overall impact that was here at that time
But if it comes then look at what we have in it also.
The commission that went to sleep became a benefit clean.
In this also we have 5 big if
In profitability
22% of friends that 22% absolutely not because
He has now been selected to tour the planet.
We must come here immediately.
Good growth in property
We hoped that our subscribers
Because because of Prince we
This mantra is here with good hope.
UPS was also set to max
So friends
We are constantly tracking this
Look at this company, profit growth is good
No
Not there.
Let's talk about the future because of this.
what impact does it have on the estimates and
The thing you have to do is limit profit growth.
Because of this, the face is under a lot of pressure and the future
Estimates: Now let's talk about oil
I saw that in 2019,
4590 oil till we shift and life style
will put the site back
Tomorrow's morning sunshine lies in profitability
Profitability weakens to 1360 in 2021
Our numbers will decrease because India will get eight
This stock is available to us in the correction board.
We are getting what we are expecting this year
There is life time profit
Watch the whole thing till the end, slowly we get into it
It will give while going towards positive but still whatever
Expectation in profit according to us
Because of this, we also have some
By 2030, we will develop Delhi's 14,000 crore-worth
Talk to this channel
Subscribe
Tax
take
So there is no problem
Jhaal now talk afternoon systematic mission such
Which often where should I invest in fire?
So no, I am investing more expensively.
I am not investing much
After coming here I reply perfectly
If it was fine then we would have seen the clear delivery and
Holiday TV channels according to our
Price leaving family is the same in 2030
If we do the family statement of this company, it is 24
I will give around 201 and by 2035 my
5 and a half puddings
That has been our family special song
That
Now that this is done, let's take our fundamentals.
This time for technical NH8 time to chart
If we look at it, we will see it in correction
But we're already here.
If she gives the print then please our
Correct time questions are not coming well
If we don't make corrections,
Friends, this was the time duration
Here, if we look at that 50 km
Almost like we should bike in it.
Penguin juice and target that if I talk
So by the end of this year we are targeting 720
can
This happened yesterday morning, now we should talk to you.
What percentage should be invested in the sector
Friends, we want 375 Akshay because we
2 percent interest has been charged on such
General
Hit like and we get it
Friends, this
It happened and this is it, friends.
It was on the face
Exactly what I say, someone of their own
my friends
That this is a great presentation, thank you brother
SEBI came into the emerging industry and
SBI and HDFC Life Kya Bolte Ho
That
If
If there is someone, he is absolutely
Definitely he is also a
Click
If you do, our channel
Subscribe
If you didn't do it, how big could it be?
searched
Thank you so much I would like to know that
After joining with Profit you will get a
In research
Now it would be better if Sir, I had Kajol.
I have set only two guru mantras
My brother is the first in my life
During call boy when I many times
Listen to Value Bank's Do It In Growth
Everyone should do this here, we have our fundamentals which
The stadium made profits towards our Guruji.
We have learned that we prepare in advance.
Lee has completed the stock pick-up time from America.
The possibility that the MLA from earlier would now introduce us to
It's fall correction time and we start
Let it be done and as soon as the rally comes our
Going to spend time with family
And
The second thing which is most important is that if
If he is a minister then I tell him this, this is my life
Is the best and first learning hand mixer
Victims Message Karo of Begumpet Urban
Estate when I voted not in.
mood that I similar story
Financial Planning and Knowledge
stock market then
happens in college
If it is not 13, everyday we get better
We will keep moving forward every day and when your time
Whatever presentation was there last time and today, in this
Watch your presentation shine
and it requires a lot of hard work and we can say that
can
it
What happens will always happen
It was that
in between
If the price of petrol increases then all this
things and things move
Stay and
Due to which it
by doing both
Important and channel subscribe
Do it if it's a very good
deepening in every quarter and the real
Look at what I did or my presentation
Most of the people who buy HDFC Life
You must have taken it too, I will tell you the bank.
Brothers, it may be BJP
Gave him the beach because he hasn't walked in 2 years
from this you saw after how many minutes
I am running HDFC Life Insurance Company.
General Apna Fee General Musharraf's Companies
Now that you all knew that this
This is not the time to ask how far you have come.
Time to know your challenger bank
How can you forget to read now, you will get profit
I am not, if there is understanding
I never worry that I have here
I am stuck here, what should I do?
Have they been clear to themselves?
The whole time I saw dosa coming time
The demand is good, will you take any tension?
Whether the name of the insurance is life or general demand
Bastar and tagged profitability such a pro
If it comes then it gets spoiled for 12 years now when
If it improves, you will see it for six-seven years.
Continuum is beautiful that and once all this city
Let's continue for some more time
Then running after him, this is the right time
It happens to take a flat tax for the entire time
Such a great presentation you made
Majority points all over the cover on your side by
Like clearly told that profits are good
No, this is what we expected.
Clarity is needed but it is made
I swear it's great I hope so
He is doing very well for you and your
Everyone benefited from the performance Stretch Thank
You might be a great going toe
Thank you sir, this is for all the students who
Because of the presentation
He is a professional presentation
I am a fan of Papa Cheezi from Visakhapatnam.
Our senior most presenter is and 1 liter.
He is a civil engineer and from there he bought land.
And another one who knows finance completely
I also did not have any background, I was a civil engineer
So whatever their presentation will be
If he remains on his back today, this disrespect will be the fourth
Friends, today's company is Dev Music
From the industry, today we can say that
Our maximum focus today is on emergent leadership.
Because the real money that is made is
If it is made in the real estate industry then
Welcome Parthasarathy ji's problem
Visakhapatnam
Grading System
That we the candidates are from Visakhapatnam
Welcome to Andhra Pradesh.
PCMC Quarter Result
When about your support now in NET education
will welcome to all
Look friends
Who is my mentor Guru Peeth Hai
Because of this we have learned a lot today.
First we will discuss about this
So when do you know about CMC result?
Get out friends
to discuss any company tax first before
Please tractor and will look two decades ago this
Asset Management has come to India
I will see before that what the market
The faces that market the city in this
Total 80 out of this which is main
I want Twenty20 and Next
The lens is
he has a strong
Out of this Aditya Birla Mutual Fund has invested Rs 3000.
Having more
60 Its to this market and next sales
We will see this in
I want 250 bastards
RS
600 on flights
that Aditya Birla Jhala is around 500 and 1000
Get more profit from the phone
I have so much back
NAC Starrer One India 350 and Aditya Birla
Lyxeji All
Of the NAAC rates, return on equity is
from so that I like it from this so
CMC and Name India
That's 1.1 today only Kapoor points 72
The point of TLC is so A, look guys.
Return paper resume previous song
so equity is now
meant the score was
went to school
Your net profit
And yes management of your profit from this
In
Ghee number
Subscribe to
Look, his mother is also in his adopted company.
Will any company see my voice? Pots Investment
Before doing it, look at your own
The city from which I have done this is sales.
that if you look in the country
that exhibition
If you look in the Bluetooth settings section
Art that started in Tooth on One
It just happened from the side 2018 or 264
Subscribe Last 20 Years More Like This
Sapna will not even notice that the company has
So after that happened profits of
The company was profitable
In
Work
From then until now
What does it mean
at school
Net Profit Margin
In
also at once
It was broke but the profit is huge
Look friends, this is reserved by the company.
See this, set it first and from 1 to now
By then it had grown by one and a half inches, its result meant this much
Well, the company's school has now expanded.
So
It is not good to go
This happened
one and a half inches and
Subscribe
do
and this channel
Subscribe
He could see the button
Our
Appointed this year the result of this tomato is ba
The previous strip is very good but
If you look at the quarter, from last week
Only three of the quarters this year
acquired
Held this time came last 50 means
They had profits but the profit was from last year to this year.
Bar 90 A
And the running has also reduced, two agar of this thing
profit
If there is no profit in the morning then it means business
It was not good like this
That we will see its current end, which current
If we look at the train and the station, we will see the current
And if you look at the four chords at the back,
No selfies in the middle of the forest quarters
Smoke and financials had reached 14% and
365 in this quarter, looking at this tender, we
Expecting 100 percent in this match
And if you look at the profit, last year test
You can add 4% more to this in one
Five percent by the financial year and this
Poster Me Ne Infection - Pack It Up Hum Log
If we are continuing, that too will happen
March-March will be up 60% if it happens on the far side
profit sharing as
This year will be and
What happened in this, see friends according to this
Apna Ko Jo and Halt will see
Hello friends, I want to say something about this.
Since the last three years with heavy
Industries Mute Two
More names than A Boy Departure
Profit Circuit Effective
Soft Dough Kashmir
and
Very nice right now
subscribe and one thing in it
The profit that is made in
so
were appointed
handed over the remaining 2.5 of his 2.1 which this
This time the elderly people are salivating over it.
It would be great
We will look into it further
Come subscribe and
120 from Joe
Zor Ka Your Feet 14210
30 to 60 more profits in 1432
These are the classes that we are requesting.
If the first one is in my mind then these
in condition
205 more
About
I am expecting this again
Share holding pattern
8.6% and 2% and the retail
And friends on the back
That the first six percent of LIC will be in this March
They increased the electric value by 2%.
Banks are doing this about this dream
People who know what to do when
The group can learn from this, see what it is
According to technical start, we
They have to do land and next year
avatar cut that looks so
₹500
We can make good profits from this.
We are just ghee
That's a question that has been arising for the past year.
People made 2% vote for investors
As he was looking for his profit, we
People have thought it's okay to erase the reason why less
Even if the cost is gone, it will still happen
There are others but there is no pocket collector.
So for this problem you just sit and
They have been hired for one percent of it.
But friends only for education proposal
has made
I pay this front's body
Presentation Emerging Industry and
You have clearly stated that ownership
The profits are not that good, hence the shares
If it is not working then many people's tip
It seems that you should start this bike but
When we add this way you did it
If this chapter is there, then there is clarity.
What is the current situation in the Quarterly?
The results give us clear directions.
Purpose of Friends Lives Right Here on Television
We check the demand of the channel and
Let's see the profit situation that your
Profits always put sorry of your city
Price always up for profit and on GPS
If you depend, then a great presentation.
Along with this, ask Papa ji to learn this also.
I would like to have this much mother after retirement
You did this course and what did you get from it?
I have learned about this from you guys.
then guide the
Yes yes thank you Mile ji see
There should be life in it and there should be a professional of your own
Hmm, that's fixed now.
Cricket decisions and swimming on Thursday
And cricket is a discovery in anyone.
Without search, without winter there is no life in the sky
I would not have been
Ghrit we found out I am lucky and native of peace
Take it this way it looks good that's why we
When you reach the stage
If there is no mantle
If that is nothing like what is happening today
People will not even know about it
From
We used to know about these general insurances a lot earlier.
his Buddhist what is happening why
He suddenly becomes nervous and
My mentor and Reddy, this is my heart
Thanks climb
Whatever we do in the profit attack
He has an account and never shares any of the below
This is mine without asking
Instant voice messages and WhatsApp
Message
Friends, there is no need to panic, just a little
If it happens, you don't need to worry.
can do it by
Subscribe
regarding
they use
Karna Point Name
Look at this, in my childhood I was into cricket.
He was very fond of cricket and was great in it.
Border from Australian World Champion
Ricky Ponting Ricky Ponting and David Boon
This is how we are in a team of Steve and Polo
One in the profit soil
My
My friends, a group of them, Amarnath
Amarnath Puri in this Prashant Khare and one
He is a great player and with this snake
I enjoy working and my
Magic mantra
Subscribe Vikas does it well
Stay with the team and subscribe to Meghwal
15 Minute Thank You Once Again
Thank you
All of this means your age.
student of
from them
in hatred
So I would like to request that
it is theirs
Today, brother, first let's laugh a little bit.
If you give it then it is fine, Parthasarathi said Amarnath
Thakur has been made the Thakur of Sholay.
Go to Veervar
[Laughter]
And I was shocked when I saw my oil in the well.
Making a presentation One Ice One Record
Investment is very low for your local people
Then Abhishek may be at his partner's house.
This happens because of
That presentation was great for you and it
It was challenging that I challenged myself because
I will do it, today you take three companies with you.
Root then thanked him after the number 10 rally.
And this oil company is Govind
After that everything was perfect live na General Motors
HDFC Tak Live Na ICC General Maze Pe
That profits were affected and are affected now
Let's go for Serum C which Pratham ji told us
Wastage is 1% (12%), anyone can take credit.
The power is very big in the last few years now 10
When the exam was made worth lakh crores, I think
Sometime around 2014, most people cared about
10 lakh crores crossed oh my god how much it has increased
Is it tomorrow for the elders or look now 2022 35
lakh crore and one of the entire mutual fund
to talk
From where did you say she is going to the same house, meaning downstairs?
Arun's album is being released but companies
Whoever appeared in the exam from MC company
Profitability is there since the fabric is there
As soon as the norms were changed, on their own strength
Explain what changes were made in the battle of
This will increase the profits and profits of Live General's company.
Business will grow
This machine has double changes clear that one
In your MP, at that time, the new people of Sidhi
Norms by him increased the investor's liter
But if the profitability of the company has come down then
You have seen this expectation, it is in demand.
You should never lack whatever you have
You invest in companies if Ishwar Singh
It should be a prestigious group, but this
Intermediate exams are not being conducted.
I smoked cigarettes because of which he
The weightage has been reduced but it is a positive thing.
I will share it in advance, the city is enough for you
This price is below but bad results were avoided.
This is not based on research but it surpasses the results.
He has given that this is the top HDFC cheap one
There is no doubt that there is definitely a layer of yours.
Whatever I saw in the comment box Ramesh
Babu is agony that he asked war tv
HD MP Area 21.3 Life Long Term
First of all, you are a great company.
HDFC has invested in MCD
The best is no doubt about SBI Leader
1 second number company update DSC this machine
There is no match for their profitability in
Not there.
Very good at everything I've done
told that
New Norms Work Profitability Down
If so, you will have to be prepared for this also, but you
Whatever is written 2120 has gone back, no worries
I think we can reach the clear end.
Recover up to ₹3000 carefully
Listen, I am not saying that HDFC
AMC will impose lifetime high, it seems difficult now
It's been a little while, until it spreads, it's good for everyone.
Don't expect a lifetime until you give me sleep
But 3002 is normal but right now you should look at 1803
If you look at it next year, you will definitely make a profit.
When you find out if this company is good, then see
Still, you get consistent profits
If you get oil then there is problem in installing it.
in this company thank you very much i am hopeful
Whatever Patthar ji talked to you people about
So this guide items proper kumar will
Thank you when thank you thank you
Thank you
Friends, the presentation
From Haridwar
Subscribe and
The whole one who for a lot of money
In terms of money, I would like to request
that he is in about Kajaria Ceramics
do it then
I am in a hotel punctured
Hey friend, thank you, where is the answer?
A clearer now my voice that this is a great when
Hello everyone, my name is Anil.
I am a Pal from Haridwar, Uttarakhand.
I serve in a government job and I
This premiered in June 2020
Institute Power Profits From Its Say
So friends, today we were connected
11 Chapters Left Side Slide Show
son, thank you so much
if so
On behalf of the tractor that we are trying to harm today
He is going to Future Home Furnishings and
Friends, today it is about flooring as we
We know that this acid and sector
There was no source for a long time, so now
It has been seen that very bumper results have come.
Whatever real estate company has
So this is our sector, real estate.
Here's a clip from the movie that we're very excited about.
Looking seriously, there are many things inside it.
We have already talked about multibaggers.
If you can, then the company we are talking about today
The name of the project is Kajaria Ceramics.
So
If you look at the tiles,
Our World Wide Joe Conjunction
The scenario is that they will see that China is involved in all this.
Brazil is number one and All are second.
India at number three, if India makes a mistake
If you look at the tax, you will see nine percent and
If you check your demographic status
If we do it then it will happen between China and us.
There is not much difference by population.
If there is an in-will demand in any of our sectors
I am seeing the benefit of which in all these
companies are getting and if we and in this
If we move forward, we will have four in this sector.
We find companies like Kajaria in one of them.
There is a height form, it is also a very good
The company is a Response India and HIL.
vision and cement seats are made on it
We will see forty seven percent of Kajaria
What is the total market share of
If we go further in the tractor, we will
If you look at the cells, there is a cell send.
The leader company in this is ready for you.
This 370
He made a fortune of around Rs 500 crore.
Demolished this year and will see profits
So in this
Both have made a profit of Rs 3333 crore while
This is a very small company which is good
Which does work worth Rs 210 crore SL
Each other means this is the product of this
Which has no relation with Kazia.
But the company is also very good.
And after that, if we wait five years here
If you look at it, you will see that
Due to the presence of small companies in it,
There seems to be a lot of opposition to the channel.
If we look at Kazia in this, then he
We have about 6% of this for 5 years.
Sales sees every day that we will move forward later
So its profit tax CAGR is
Ours is ten percent and yours is rice.
If you look at it, it will be 22% if you look a little further.
You should have a very clear picture in the slide.
will know why we are sitting on top of Kazia
In this we are engaged in quality analysis
If you click on it, you will see that what is in it
Margin is that best of Kajaria so we
In a way, it is considered a sector leader.
Let us see if the margin of sector liters
If it is the best then why should we separate ourselves from it?
Investing for a long time
We have to live and keep doing it and the way we
Proper Play was telling that the haunting was real
The state itself is one again
If Multi is on its way to becoming accused, now we
If we look at the return of
Equity that our shareholders receive
If there is any remaining money, how can I spend it?
If the company invests, it will generate seventeen
It is required for percentage, it has 18 percent
So the accused is almost equal but if this
Quality is why we give our employees
After filling the pick, we will see the ICR.
So shot A which is your ICR here
37% means India which
Bad times are behind us now
Was there a call from Butt in Bauraya or before that?
This ICR has a great value in medicine.
goes and every fundamental analyst
The same size works on CR and
Kept such companies in your portfolio
Whose advertisement is good, he moves ahead
Let's go friends, then we will see in this
to equity ratio so in this you will see
Only five percent of Kajaria means this
This is such a low debit as per my scooter
Five percent is there, the rest are quite tall.
Because of which our situation is like Kazia
remains on top of
After that we will discuss Behavior and Lessons in it.
We will see about it from our friends who
Smell of this who is the media's loud superstar juice
Let's mute it or test match it
Akshay Kumar is there and now it has the reserve
We will see, sorry, this light has moved ahead.
If you look here, you will see that this company
Only a reserve of Rs 60 crore has been kept since 2003.
Which has increased to Rs 216 crores as of today.
It is done
After that we will move ahead and this 21 which this
The multibagger that we are talking about
See the result friends, trust here
It is increasing and this money is falling on all of us.
Either this new question among the people
or return it to us as dividends
It is available
After that, if we look at the sales growth
So in the last 20 years, from 2003 to 2022
Its a consistently village in me now side only
Its trend has been very positive.
A little bit in between, 2000 basic in this
There is little liquid and because of that I got shocked.
But this time because of fuel prices
You will see how fantastic the management was.
He
The time of sales itself means lifetime only.
who imposed it while quite challenging
It was time, this is how I made profit
Friends, you will also see that it is in profit.
They don't even mean competitors.
So in the chapter and he achieved height high
Life itself has also given them profit in this
One time you will see how challenging the situation is.
After that he delivered so well
When all four will be out of Bigg Boss
On the other hand, our economy is
If the state of the world is normal
If it goes then we will see about their profit.
This is the margin of acting, you will run like Rocky
They are running consistent margins
Friends, because this is a good company.
quality that it can increase its margins
Maintains composure no matter what the situation is
You'll see 11 percent and 10 percent days.
The entire company in the last two-three years, I mean
Margin became active and she started making losses.
This company is quite good at its
Consistency is due to
And then we'll talk about business lighting.
Let's see friends, here we will see that
Its cell on the side that comes in it
13,500 cows in 2035
will rise closer to 279 and
2030 Yours in 2030
1626 and your year to come
Its I, our shell, is again
It will take more than a lifetime to do this
If we look at the profit, there will be profit in it.
Our
929 in 2030 and 475 again in your life
It may take time, even GPS can
There has been a very good growth and share value
Let's see friends, this is just the recent time.
One of my fair value passed by and went away
The stock has seen a strong rally and is still
This is enough
It is at a reasonable price as it
The result has come in quarterly form, so you
will see that its
The value is quite good, I am Ambedkar in it.
We will talk about the cost which is lost in the major cost.
Which is 20% of the total market
Raw Material is and Power & Tools is
percent, now friends will see the stock in it
Its share on the internet is also 27 percent.
If you like Stocks & Trade and Fuel
You will see that it is very powerful
There has been an increase due to whose help their
The market may have been at the margin of these, but
Actually we did not find out about it.
This is how the management has managed it
that we have any difference in margin in this
But as it increases your fuel cost and
Stock in trend thousands of medical formalities
You will see that there will be towers like the efforts of
The numbers it has are even more impressive.
We will come back in the next quarter in a proper way.
I'll track it next quarter, guys.
Now we will share its results again in this.
If we talk about holding pattern then in this
You will see that your stake in what is
He has increased the mother and promoter's
The building is approximately equal, so we will see that
which makes everyone believe in it
did not make any significant changes to his building
did and it just in it and the meter burst
One has enhanced its perfect position
And then we'll go to the technical analyst.
Friends, we are seeing in this that the
We have 1 million zones and yours is 1000.
Amit H gets Rs. 740 to Rs. 740
Mill can add and short term target
Our first time in this was around 1600.
I think I will book profits.
that in 2023
Someone must come up with a special map and
After this we will see so many Patnas in it
part of our portfolio is a
can be from one to two percent because in this
There are other sector leader companies like
that is unsuccessful, leading to the sale of Sheela Forms
I have a company you will see the company this company
Look at the size of this ad in the world
If you are a gas company then you can know about its potential.
Now we can think about it, we can understand it.
I would like to give a disclaimer that this
Whatever our presentation is, it is only
This is for study purpose, it contains details of sale-purchase
You can do your own study or
Then seek advice from a financial advisor.
Thank you friends this is my
Presentation was App Investing Jaye
Shakti Anil ji, great presentation
You have your government job and tremendous meaning
That the lowest tax for the research you have done
There are two more Kajrare workers rolling rotis and going ahead
will also remain because in the real estate sector
Demand is visible and sales are as you mentioned.
Told that things are going very well and making profits
If it is going well then I will thank you for it
I would like to say thank you and I would like to thank you for a
I would like to request you to tell me this
that you should mother before depositing class and
What do you learn after joining the class?
What a difference this approach has made now
I went and thanked you sir, first of all you helped me
Thank you very much for turning this around
Choke Hai Balance Job Profile Very
It's different, I work from the side
No matter how many projects there are, even today
I also went to the office and returned at 6:30.
A little work remained to be done on this
My 11 any way next result that all
I will complete it and my learning sir is very helpful.
It has been wonderful, I have changed a lot sir
after joining with and meaning their
It is a commitment, isn't it, sir, it is his responsibility.
I would like to tell you two or three things.
The discipline that the government has is mind blowing.
It means he commented on something.
If you do it then that too is mind blowing.
Confidence is amazing, meaning the market
How do we update these dreams?
What is said today, the market will tell tomorrow.
If this is how it happened then it is very amazing.
It is a thing and we bring a lot of things to Delhi
We used to learn the morning ad in our group
The message you post is a great thing.
Daily market report we get it
And everyone said that we have to live in liters.
These golden words sir golden work this
Leadership Quality Growth: Just Look at These 3 Things
The market is nothing, sit comfortably
As Sir says, keep calm and take care of your money.
If it is made then it will happen, but all this panic will not arise.
If there are three or four of them running in the market,
Mary and I will always be grateful for this.
I will take it sir, it is from your entire team, yes thank you.
U Anil ji, whatever the UPA government always says
That these waiting are stress free
Initially we should not have anyone
It seemed because every time trading and
The remaining calls will be made by the toppers of ₹2 each.
If messages used to circulate, then now the problem also
We can do these, all these are schools, please
If you got it because of Sir, then that grade will go to the teacher.
I would like to request that Kazia
Ceramics with a heart above
Remember brother, look at all yours today.
There is a company, see, like the soil company in the middle
But the final challenge had been done, so in the meantime
of the team whose profits and business are such
It won't work but we used to mix
But both Root Mobile and 1000 or so
It is a perfect medicine, we will do a time blast, that's why
Like Jalkot Anil in Kajaria Khajuria village
The brother explained it very well.
Their fuel also remains in a deserted place
Death of the inverter as it is already on
The prices will not increase but due to inflation
If fuel cost should not increase then like
There are metal companies, I feel a little scared there.
Whenever the Guru feels that his expenses increase
Cement companies are afraid to go
Similarly, Khajuria is also afraid that crores
has increased or the cost of the video has increased
It may have happened but it did not happen, they were surprised
First of all, this moment demand is tremendous
Slide that shows the cell that has been raging
that India's Pir 122 City is doing very well
which were also in your presentation today.
Is everyone from Mega City getting into this?
And Anil Bhai, from which city are you coming?
Haridwar is very Haridwar Nashik
honey until over the off birth
Haridwar
The modern ones were very small
This does not mean that only big cities
In
Protein 1222 sentiment should come when
Country
And this is what you see, which
The demand for them is so huge that they can get it from there.
If profit is a good company then demand was found
He took full advantage of it and made a profit.
Now let us take its value into account.
So I have full hope that Anil Bhai will do something
The hesitations were deep that
of 2017
When Anil Bhai showed the result of his portal
Till I come to present it, see you after a cup of tea.
will have passed
per full time
Very good
To tell you the truth, I really liked your job.
If he takes it from there, then some work remains but
All the people here throughout the day
If people have problems, they should all leave their jobs quickly.
People sat down, but the presentation you made.
Someone felt like I was
This is the quality of maturity that you
Do you know
Subscribed and very well done
Congress has
I want one more thing from the stars and as many
All are people too
In Golden Line I sent it everywhere at 90
For it is normal or it is normal, it is normal
We panic in the stocks that sleep well
I don't thank you like this sir, Jai Hind Jai
Durga
9th Jai Hind Thank you when next jo
Presentation is that tweet and a profit.
The most popular format
Amazing Amarnath Thakur who is in Gujarat
He is from Ahmedabad and markets them himself.
is a training institute which is spoken
College of English and Computer
if so
Amarnath ji, I think this is quite a lot
Presented art near 50 and
Quarterly results for you President
and to the entire team of Profit Permit who
PPT is presentation software.
There is a presentation in it that one should always refuse to live.
It is right and complicated like Reliance
Subject which also includes retail
Petroleum also comes, whatever comes
Multiple businesses that are compatible with
Aman Raj about the presentation to all of us
I welcome Amarnath ji, you will guide me
Thanks cross clear screen is visible
Very good sir, number one, thank you sir
Hello friends, I am Amarnath Thakur.
Profit from it key from Ahmedabad Gujarat
I heartily welcome you all from
Friends, my presentation today is
He is India's biggest company Reliance
It is up to the industries, so come friends, let us
Friends, if you know Reliance Industries
Reliance Industries Quarter One
The result is out, how is it?
We will know how the sector is doing.
Because Reliance Industries is
Their business spans many different segments.
Reliance Industries
Before going to Sector-47 Quality
In the text Ananit Historical Data Analysis
What did the company do for the future?
What is the vision for current and future trains?
Technical analysis will look at time eggplant
So friends, first of all, if I tell you
My Learnings That Remember Me with Future 2
It's been years
I did away with yes sir and
Learning is not a very powerful class.
Because of which today I have such confidence
I am able to give a presentation to my friends.
First, if we look at factor analysis
First of all, from friends to company 39
The first thing to know is that the sector
Is it in demand or not, believe it friends
If the sector itself is not in demand then no matter how much
If the company is good then it will not grow.
So friends, let's know about the sector.
Friends, if you want to check the meaning of Reliance then
It's a bit difficult at first
If we look at India, there are a total of about 5
There are thousands of companies in the list, from which if we
See
So the surprising thing is that Rs 20 lakh crore
Which of the following is the first of its kind in the market?
When the company arrives, friends, if we here
If you see, the market cap of Reliance is around 116
The TCS wallet is worth Rs 60 crore.
lakh crore HDFC Bank Infosys Tata
ICICI Bank's six crore rupees spread further
If we look at the market cards of the bank here
Look at the friends, in every company
I see a huge difference in
But if I ask you guys which one is the most
First market cap of 20 lakh crore
Which company will touch, so here we
It is clear that Reliance comes first.
If there is someone inside for 20 lakh crores
Whose company becomes the market, then there
Reliance Industries
Friends, if we look at Reliance
The market cap is 16 lakh crores and today we
Why has Bharti Airtel and
With the demand, friends, today I will tell you
I would like here that those who are in the market
Reliance Industries has received that Rs 16 lakh
One of the forts near the Crore Market
Reliance is not a business, it is a bar business
industries and that whole of industries
Diversified business includes oil and gas
Retail and Jio are their major businesses.
Singh is getting a lot of business
Oil and Gas friends, theirs is very old
And settle business tab retail and Jio whose
These people are doing a great job inside right now.
So if we look at some of the totals of all this
16 lakh of Reliance Industries in total
A market cap of crores is approximately two
Bharati of the market of crores folded
Airtel and about 2.5 lakh crore
The market has a brain, friends.
See the shape of the sector and
that if we talk about today, then the most
Where does the demand come from, so friends, retail
and digital transformation
The highest demand comes from
Because Reliance has lost its old business
Setup Oil & Gas along with it
He spoke on digital transformation in retail.
They came forward and did a great job.
have been
Friends, if we talk about total sales then
It will be almost the first company in India which
Making sales of approximately Rs 1 lakh crore
This means a lot of money from a very big cell.
Bharti is the company that is increasing its sales
If we look at Airtel, it is worth around Rs 1 lakh crore.
Demand is approximately Rs 30,000 crore.
Self is
Friends, if we compare here
To Reliance
With demand and Reliance Industries
One part is Reliance Retail and demand which
If we compare it with them then total
If we look at August break, Reliance's 1600
But friends, I would like to tell you here that
Computer brains are Reliance stores,
They are small and there are about 800 ads in Water One.
have done
If you look at the area, it is approximately 3.3
million square feet area and sales
If we look at
Reliance alone is worth approximately Rs 2 lakh crore.
Reliance is getting more water from retail
And if I look at it, sales of around Rs 6000 crore
Reliance has got more from Reliance Retail
If you compare to demand, then demand is approximately
There are 21842 in India but these are big
There are stores, friends, and about 11.5
million square foot space and sales
If you look at it, the sensor costs around Rs 3000 crore.
If we look at Quarter One, friends, it's close.
Computers worth Rs 1000 crore have been sold
If we look at the other company of Reliance
This is Reliance Digital which is called
And Bharti Airtel friends here I
I would like to say that it is surprising that
Reliance Jio has been in India for almost 5 years.
And if we look here, 1 lakh
If you are doing crores of rupees business right now then here
We get a very good signal from
that the ability to do business in management
The ability is very good, almost
Half of India is their subscriber and there
If we look at Bharti Airtel, this decade
back company but now
We have sales of only Rs 1.25 lakh crore here.
And if Bharti Airtel friends are watching
If I talk to you here, x17
Within countries within Asia and Africa
This is their business and Reliance Jio's
This business is only within India.
Friends, if we talk about profit then
This will be India's first such listed company.
Who is a profit of approximately seventy thousand crores
If we look at what she is doing,
What is Reliance getting from the new business?
So friends, I would like to tell you that their
This is an old business, they will take this mask.
They are earning a good income but new
If we look at the new business, then from retail they
100 crore profit is being received completely
So if we look at the demand, it is approximately
There is four to five times more profit and Jio
If we look at it from now, if we look at it in 5 years,
There is also a profit of about Rs 4,500 crore.
They are getting Bharti Airtel's services from here.
See Dhamtari's profit demand of Rs 180 crore
If we look at it, the profit is around Rs 150-140 crore.
Friends, we can see now friends, if
If we look, we have seen the most
Which is the biggest company?
You saw the sales, you saw the profits, now we see
Quality analysis, friends, first of all
Margin If we look at the cost of doing business
How much money does the company take home after
If we look at the margins of Reliance
Airtel has around 9.4% at 7.1%.
Shankar Demand's approximately 5 person profit
margin is
If we talk about dating potential
Friends, here is a very good
A strong sign of demand suggests that approximately
If you have the money to do it on a 20x time date
I can see clearly here friends that
the mind which is
Not a big company but a fabric
The company is very good and it also has
If there is demand, there is no need to worry.
Yes friends, if you look at Airtel, there are tabs.
So there is a time and Reliance SIM is next
Time is ICR now friends if we look
debt to equity ratio you like I
I told you that the IC of demand is 814 time.
So there is no dip on the brain at all.
Africa and the Hundred Percent Quality Company
Business growth is also getting good and profit is also increasing.
It is getting better
Friends, if we look there, here
If we look at Airtel in front of the Dead Sea
178 Person Back to Equity Ratio means one
If the usage date is above Bharti Airtel
Friends, before investing here, we
Will you have to be a little careful or Reliance
If we look at it, it is about 124 people.
The debt-equity ratio is good.
Not that good and not that bad either
But what about them is that the sales are very big.
The profits are also very good.
And speaking of health, friends.
Reliance has a return of around nine percent on
Equity constitutes approximately ₹100 crore of Bharti Airtel
12.5% ​​and demand is approximately 11:00 persons
Return on equity is increasing
Hello friends Historical gives massage
do that the part match company did that it
It is very important to know that the fifth
What did the company do to let us know?
What the company can do in the future
So friends, if the segment wise revenue
If we look at the growth, then all three of their main segments
That is the GDP and performance of the whole of India
The other one is doing all these double digits.
Group inside Agarwal to Capital Chemical
If you look at the business, it has grown from about 157 people.
If we look at retail, it is growing by 22% and digital
If we look at the service, discounts are starting from 22%.
If so, this
Very good lines for Reliance.
There is growth in all their businesses.
Is
Friends, if we look at the sales growth here
So at one time a juice company worth Rs 2800 crore
Sales was doing such a big joint today, how?
So friends, we are seeing clearly here.
That today in 2022, it will be worth approximately Rs 5 lakh crore.
Sales company is doing and this fruit if we
If you look at it, Life Time High Schools were also set up.
Friends, if the company makes a profit
If we talk about profit then also if we look at 84
If there is a profit of thousand crores in 20 years
Let's see it reach seventy thousand crores
Gaya means voting percentage when 15*
Make profit this year, it is a good thing that life
I have also invested time and high profit and friends
Reliance on very good things here
If I may tell you, sometime in my history
It has not lost much
Correction came
The pendant is fine but never lose its history.
Reliance did not launch it friends.
If you look at the company's results, here
Can be seen in very strong reserves
It is worth around Rs 8 lakh crore.
Reliance has that 58 per cent CAGR
Reliance's reserves are 50 times larger than
Now friends, if we look at the margin, the margin
Also this raw material is around average 90 per cent cut.
Reliance has maintained it in the long term
Hello friends, now it is the turn of the Major
Where does the cost go in the business?
Friends, if we look at the major cost
If we analyze, then their biggest cost is
Is
It is the material cost above which
It costs me the most friends
Suppose if Reliance Industries
If you want to invest, if you want to invest
If I look at the investors of my peer group
The promoter has about 150 one-person tech
Mutual Fund FIR has around 120.4%
Insurance has approximately one person and
Retail has a Thirteen Person paper.
So friends, if we look at the current train then
Is the train visible now?
Reliance protested that even if it did not
Friends, if
If we look at the current trend of cent profit
So
If so, then 250 is like
that is 54.72
that in test one and profit for this person
If we look at the group of cells in the ninth
20% profit growth annually with shift
Thatipur has seen 4% sales growth and
26.8 quarter of profit one but see we
So sales growth was fifty percent and
41.70 profit growth has happened so see
Friends, here the last chapter is less
If you analyze it, it is very good here.
Signs are received that the company has done a lot of business
It has grown well and the trophy is very
Increase your tax in the future with good growth
See
So forward
2823, the company's sales growth is 14%.
We can expect such a big and thirty five
The company's profit growth in percentage terms
We can expect this to increase
Hello friends, in the future we are hoping
Is Reliance really not that much?
If you have done your business then will you proceed further from here?
If you keep hoping instead of giving up hope
Friends, this small company has grown to such a big company.
It has become a giant of a big company and can become one.
If you look at the acceptance of the future
To friends
So one of their habits is such that if you
If you see the results, you will see
New expressions will appear, meaning the company
And actor Ali and In Organic Lee both
The way the company is growing, it's very good.
This is a sign of Reliance Industries, friends.
If we look at sales as future trains
So this year we'll see that for friends
It will be the first company to have a turnover of Rs 10 lakh crore.
will pass oil
If we look at 2030, it will be
133 lakh crore seal song and if by 2030
If seen in five, then it is around Rs 60 crore.
The company will do sales only if friends
When it comes to profit, the feature of profit
If we look at the train, this year we will see that approximately
The company was able to make a profit of Rs 9000 crore
If we look at 2030, there will be around 250
Make a profit of crores and if we talk about 2035
If we do this then it is a company worth around Rs 5 lakh crore.
If we make a profit, don't you think so friends?
You know that Indian companies are also Chinese and American
company like
It will be a big one. Hello friends, if we look ahead.
Share Value So if we within 2023 if
If we want to do it, we can go back to 1968.
Bike Par Fateh 2030 Has Affirm Values
Curry Band
Sheds is becoming her and look inside 2035
So
Shades of the fair value price of his company
Friends, Bhringraj is being made, if we see
So approximately
9860 in the middle while Stark is the app so it
Now I must activate Sales and
If there is proper texture then it is not necessary that
But if his unity goes in vain
If we get a chance in this then definitely
We should invest here in the near term
If we look at the target, it will be Rs.21 and
How many people do we have inside the portfolio?
Friends, first of all we will see here
But the company made 12345 times the money.
Is
That the company made money which is around 450
So here we have a good sign
It seems that our wealth will remain in the future as well.
will form
Friends portfolio weight and here we are
will give trick choice because diversified
The business is oil and gas, the business is retail.
It arrived and here we saw digital
If their business also comes then it will be of three persons.
weightage here we should give and one
Invest here for long term with patience
But you can do the disclaimer here friends
But Barath would like to tell that this presentation
Of lightning purpose and skill development
Those present at the programme could know that
Indian best business which is how to protest
are doing
Thank you friends, today's my
There was a presentation on that, thank you Milind.
Sir
Thank you Amarnath ji, great presentation and
Today's presentation in a different format
Enjoyed everyone's affection very well
and subscribed query to Reliance
It has increased so much because Mukesh Ambani
If there is a businessman for India then there is an investor
And what will you get in the group, but the growth of those
These jeans retailer who is a tremendous and
If we look at its quarterly results
So that huge protest is going on in the retail sector.
If so, a complicated business model
In your best style and in your best manner
A very festive experience explained in a very simple way
I will thank you for this, I will tell my boss
I would like to say that one thing is about Amarnath ji
She has a unique style because she is herself
If there is a teacher then it is a very complicated subject.
What You Eat Is What You Eat
This subject has been explained in a very easy way.
He has a natural ability to do so I
I would like to take a review of this Reliance
is about
and I would like to tell the officer that the body
Your influence on the whole is the highest.
But it looks cold
No, because the way you work is very difficult.
How easily you explain difficult subjects
yes this that
as it is
juice
To
Subscribe to may people
is in the middle
there you
The present religion can be said to be so big
Great cricketer, your presentation has been done
Tight is what the team made White Widow
I searched it now, it's great
Reliance Reliance Media a city at that time
Reliance, different companies
Retail is on one side
If you want to do this then
whole
explained in many ways and now
The school said that in the near future
Britain needs very large companies
By crossing over very big things
Retail
will be made
So
Subscribe and
Things are very much in the presentation that demands
Compared with Reliance Usage Voice
It is not comparable to Reliance.
Proposing boys but quality white gold
20k demand good quality so brain
Tell me about the horse and sit with the treatment.
You will sing the song of the lens, it is not like this
Which is the problem explained in one but
I would like to make a correction, Amarnath Bhai, what you said
There is news about tomatoes and Reliance, isn't there?
Square feet told from the left side
Aishwarya
added ok
Sir edition happens
Reliance's
four times with them
How many results did they achieve in security?
It is written that three million square feet
That addition to your pills
Pocket
Wonderful presentation I hope it
Which is currently small under Guava Your Reliance
You know how long I've been waiting for this target.
Was doing
Since last year, there are 320 jobs in the near future.
If the target is achieved in the term then it is a matter of happiness.
When what we thought was our target
Reliance has come and will come in the future too.
I have a lot of expectations from him, definitely.
Lower level packing can mince ginger and it
Even at the level, the field is good in my opinion.
Now I haven't seen it but at the end of my
I think it's at level three and a half or four.
I have published the result so far.
I don't want to see it, should I also check it or
So this is a lifetime and it's still going on, but then
Also, the valuation is good overall.
You will also see a better rally than the light bulb
That look at this, when this is the background of Shravan ji
If you don't have a finance background, then F-18 is
It will be very difficult for China if soon
not only
Any man can understand the running of the stock market
If he does, he feels that at least now
So
You yourself don't even know but you subscribed to it
If it is important then I will ask Amarnath ji.
I would like to see 9 newsrooms to this many
How are you
Sir actually not this
[Laughter]
If there is nothing else to do, then you can work on YouTube.
seeing seeing
No sir with a professional
The changes in life are very quick.
lie
If you do all these things, you don't realize when
until we go down into the well
What has come out is a very good thing.
If not then
Having too much time in the stock market
Despite this, people were afraid because they were afraid
It seemed that this was
Too
People
how big will it be
So he keeps doing all these things like this
come in the near future
goes
So if you like this then you must check the box.
You can also write speed in YouTube.
Till then you can add next week's
Friends, which is our presentation?
I will tell you about the companies that will be
I would like to tell you friends in the next week.
We are bringing some companies which are 7
Same evening on Sunday, August 8:00
Typing will remain and 8:00 will give you more excellent
research and the next companies will get whose
Your portfolio with weightage
If you can install then which notes are these
If the company is there, I would like to tell you this.
Friends, this is this company
I am Anil Pal Sir, who is the Supreme
We will discuss the industries whose best
Presentation today you heard Dr. Duggal
sir from patan gujarat video jise and woh
Ajnayan Amarnath to speak on Asian Paints
Ji Thakur will talk to us about Bajaj Auto.
Amarnath Thakur will be with us and decree again
Larsen & Toubro which is a separate line like
It is a big empire, talk about it
will do and most awaited and most
Creative person Ashok Sonagara ji Relax Ke
about as powerful and excellent as
If we do a presentation, I will tell all of you
I invite you to join me on Sunday in August
to 8:00 we'll all meet back and it
Companies not in our portfolio
Keep abreast of what to do
Friends, we will get information about this proposal.
We will give a 40-50 part presentation of the entire presentation.
companies cover at least our
We try to reach maximum companies
cover so that your portfolio is in it
Which company should I take and at what time?
Office - Whose office is it to increase so that your
The returns of the portfolio being invested
Yes, your speed is excellent.
So that verification is never less, you can do this
Please never miss a presentation.
Thank you Sir and today's presents.
I say if there is something in Paris then we
I definitely want to take it
A Piya Milan first benific on my tip
We clear it and apart from them I
I don't think anyone is clear about the title.
You have covered all the points very well.
If you have done this then this has been the player presentation
Or thank you so much gangster knowledge we together
Five better companies on Sunday at 8 pm
will bring a presentation and according to you
You will be able to do it with his son and you will put the plate here.
To Profit From a Family Key
I invite you all on behalf of
thank you sir